questions = [
    {
        'question': 'What colour is associated with Gryffindor House?',
        'answer': ['Green', 'Yellow', 'Red', 'Blue'],
        'correct_answer': 'Red'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Who is the oldest Weasley Child?',
        'answer': ['Bill', 'Fred', 'Ginny', 'Ron'],
        'correct_answer': 'Bill'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What did Harry call his owl?',
        'answer': ['Buckbeak', 'Aragog', 'Hedwig', 'Nagini'],
        'correct_answer': 'Hedwig'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What London train station did the Hogwarts Express depart from?',
        'answer': ['London Waterloo Station', 'London Victoria Station', 'Paddington Station', 'Kings Cross Station'],
        'correct_answer': 'Kings Cross Station'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What was the name of the Gryffindor House ghost?',
        'answer': ['Tom Riddle', 'Nearly Headless Nick', 'Rowena Ravenclaw', 'Luna Lovegood'],
        'correct_answer': 'Nearly Headless Nick'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What was the name of Hagrids dog?',
        'answer':  ['Aragog', 'Nagini', 'Frank', 'Fang'],
        'correct_answer': 'Fang'
    },
    {
        'question': 'How was Harry related to the Dursleys',
        'answer': ['Petunia was his Mothers Sister', 'Petunia was his Fathers Sister', 'Vernin was his Mothers Brother', 'Vernin was his Fathers Brother'],
        'correct_answer': 'Petunia was his Mothers Sister'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Learning what spell led to Ron Upsetting Hermione',
        'answer': ['Alohomora', 'Avada Kedavra', 'Wingardium Leviosa', 'Expelliarmus'],
        'correct_answer': 'Wingardium Leviosa'
    },
    {
        'question': 'What was the Profession of Hermiones Parents',
        'answer': ['Doctors', 'Bus Drivers', 'Biologists', 'Dentists'],
        'correct_answer': 'Dentists'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Which Student reopened the Chamber of secrets',
        'answer': ['Ron Weasley', 'Tom Riddle', 'Ginny Weasley', 'Harry Potter'],
        'correct_answer': 'Ginny Weasley'
    }

]
